<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Benchmark xmlns="http://checklists.nist.gov/xccdf/1.1" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:cdf="http://checklists.nist.gov/xccdf/1.1" xmlns:cpe="http://cpe.mitre.org/dictionary/2.0" xmlns:cpelang="http://cpe.mitre.org/language/2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:dsig="http://www.w3.org/2000/09/xmldsig#" id="com_redhat_rhsa_20141653_xml_benchmark" resolved="0" xml:lang="en-US" xsi:schemaLocation="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/ simpledc20021212.xsd http://www.w3.org/2000/09/xmldsig# xmldsig-core-schema.xsd http://cpe.mitre.org/dictionary/2.0 cpe-dictionary_2.0.xsd http://checklists.nist.gov/xccdf/1.1 xccdf-1.1.4.xsd http://cpe.mitre.org/language/2.0 cpe-language_2.0.xsd">
  <status date="2015-06-04">draft</status>
  <description>File content for OVAL file com.redhat.rhsa-20141653.xml built on 2014-10-16T10:18:43</description>
  <version>v0.0</version>
  <Profile id="Profile_Title">
    <title>Profile_Title</title>
    <select idref="xccdf_oval_com_redhat_rhsa_def_20141653_rule" selected="true" />
  </Profile>
  <Group id="Group_Title">
    <Rule id="xccdf_oval_com_redhat_rhsa_def_20141653_rule">
      <title>RHSA-2014:1653: openssl security update (Moderate)</title>
      <description>OpenSSL is a toolkit that implements the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL),
Transport Layer Security (TLS), and Datagram Transport Layer Security
(DTLS) protocols, as well as a full-strength, general purpose cryptography
library.

This update adds support for the TLS Fallback Signaling Cipher Suite Value
(TLS_FALLBACK_SCSV), which can be used to prevent protocol downgrade
attacks against applications which re-connect using a lower SSL/TLS
protocol version when the initial connection indicating the highest
supported protocol version fails.

This can prevent a forceful downgrade of the communication to SSL 3.0.
The SSL 3.0 protocol was found to be vulnerable to the padding oracle
attack when using block cipher suites in cipher block chaining (CBC) mode.
This issue is identified as CVE-2014-3566, and also known under the alias
POODLE. This SSL 3.0 protocol flaw will not be addressed in a future
update; it is recommended that users configure their applications to
require at least TLS protocol version 1.0 for secure communication.

For additional information about this flaw, see the Knowledgebase article
at https://access.redhat.com/articles/1232123

All OpenSSL users are advised to upgrade to these updated packages, which
contain a backported patch to mitigate the CVE-2014-3566 issue. For the
update to take effect, all services linked to the OpenSSL library (such as
httpd and other SSL-enabled services) must be restarted or the system
rebooted.</description>
      <check system="http://oval.mitre.org/XMLSchema/oval-definitions-5">
        <check-content-ref href="com.redhat.rhsa-20141653.xml" name="oval:com.redhat.rhsa:def:20141653" />
      </check>
    </Rule>
  </Group>
</Benchmark>

